Hasibur Rahman

Full-stack web developer

0158091900

hasib.active@gmail.com

www.hasibapp.com

Dhaka, Bangladesh



I am a professional full-stack web developer since 2018. I can design and develop any type of website, web-based application using PHP Laravel framework and Vue Js.

Starting out at the age of 17 I never stopped learning new programming skills and languages. Early I started creating websites for curiosity and just for fun as well. And then I became a good web designer with HTML, CSS, and jQuery (jQuery was a hero!). Besides Front-end development, I also explored Backend and other non-web-only technologies. This passion has since lasted and led to my decision to work as a freelance web developer. The success and fun I have in this job are immense and really keep that passion burningly alive.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Full-stack web developer

999 It | 2020 - Present

I have been working with 999 It solution for more than two year. And I learned lots of things from them. Some of are, How to work professionally, team management, and better coding structure. Primarily they uses Laravel for their backend and Vue Js for the front-end development.

Some of the projects I have done with this team.

- Sozashop (Inventory)
- Outchimp (Online Marketplace)
- Wrapmotif (Car wrapping company)

Front-end developer

Coder eyes | 2019 - 2020

Role This is a very small team where I worken as a front-end developer. That was y first real-life working experience. They make templates for Wordpresss and some other CMS management systems.

- Hexa Blog (Blog template)
- Contra (Business template)
- Agentur (Personal website)

PROJECTS

Sozahop - (Inventory)

You This is an Inventory managment application. Our team uses Laravel api for backend and Nuxt Js t manage front-end. This is the most complecated project l'have ever done. I enjoyed and learned lots of things from this project.

Outchimp - (Online Marketplace)

You This is similar to an online marketplace where a buyer can post their job offer and user can apply for the job. Our team uses Laravel api for the backend and Nuxt Js to manage front-end. Here I learned how a marketplace actually works and manage multiple authenticated user.

SKILLS

Technical

JavaScript

React/Vue

Node.js

PHP/Laravel

Object-oriented design

Professional

Effective communication

Team player

Strong problem solver

Good time management

EDUCATION

HSC in Science

Abujar Gifarih University College 2017 - 2018

SSC in Electrical

Sherpur Technical 2015 - 2016

LANGUAGES

Bangla (Native)

English (Fluent)

INTERESTS

Photography

Climbing & Hiking

Travelling

